You give me love, and we dare to do this to my heart
You give me always my surprise, so tell me tell me why
You treat me really like a toy
Baby, make a make a make up, you're my set to make up
Make it a just one that you need
Baby, love and love and love me
Love is one that's one thing, the most important thing to do
But you're killing my love, and everybody's sure
You put together my love
You give me love, and you love me forever
The places they never, I give you remember
The dreams they met, the hearts, you're killing my love
And you move this journey, put together my love
You give me love, and you love me forever
I'm gonna have a kiss with you together
I don't want to believe in love anymore
You're gonna destroy my life
I would think you'd do it come your way
You can't believe I'm your life
So tell me, tell me why
You've been a lollipop at your home
Baby, make a make a make a make up
You're my side to wake up
Baby, I just want to let you leave
Baby, I love, I love, I love me
Love is one, it's one thing
The most important thing to do
But you're killing my love
And I'm breathing strongly
What is up for anyone?
Love is forever for places
And never to keep you remember
You're killing my love
And you've been showing me
But you're killing my love
What is up for anyone?
You're killing my love
And you've been showing me
But you're killing my love
You're killing my love
And you've been showing me
But you're killing my love
What is up for anyone?
You're killing my love
And you've been loving me more
Baby, make a make up, make a make up
You're my side to wake up
Baby, I just want to let you leave
Baby, I love, I love, I love me
Love is one, it's one thing
The most important thing to do
But you're killing my love
And I'm breathing strongly
What is up for anyone?
Love is forever for places
And never to keep you remember
You're killing my love
And you've been showing me
But you're killing my love
My views aren't performing
To hinder forever
It's просто between together
I don't want't believe in love anymore
are
KILL IT
leb
You